American Song Sheets, 1850-1870 M1628.2.A5
Lilly Library
- 248. The Monitor and Merrimac. - I'm going to sing a song, I won't detain you long (7 verses and chorus.) By Chas. A Clarke. New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan kissing cupids. See Wolf 1453.
- 249. Monitor and the Merrimac. - I'm going to sing a song, I won't detain you long (7 verses and chorus.) Air.- "Yankee Doodle Dandy." Philadelphia: Johnson, n.d. Wolf 1453e.
- 250. Moonlight on the Lake. - Come away, come away (3 verses.) Philadelphia: Johnson, n.d. Not in Wolf.
- 251. Mother Dear, I'll Come Home. - Oh! mother dear, I sigh in vain (2 verses and chorus.) Sung by T. B. Prendergast, at Bryant's Minstrels, 472 Broadway, N.Y. New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan military cupid. Wolf 1462b.
- 252. Mother, Is the Battle Over? - Mother, is the battle over? (3 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan kissing cupids. See Wolf 1466.
- 253. Mother Kissed Me in My Dream. - Lying on my dying bed (3 verses and chorus.) No. 893. With a preceding narrative text, beginning: "A young soldier who was severely wounded at the battle of Antietam..." Boston: Horace Partridge, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. See Wolf 1468.
- 254. Mother Would Comfort Me. - Wounded and sorrowful, far from my home (3 verses and chorus.) No.1171. New York: J. Wrigley, n.d. Border: Wrigley military cupid. See Wolf 1472.
- 255. My Boyhood's Happy Home. - My boyhood's happy, happy home (2 verses and chorus.) Words and Music by Our Ned. New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan musical instruments. See Wolf 1495b.
- 256 My Good Old Irish Home. - Och my heart still yearns for my good ould Irish Home (3 verses and chorus.) Air - "My Old Kentucky Home." New York: Andrews, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. See Wolf 1505.
- 257. My Good Ould Irish Home. - Och my heart still yearns for my good ould Irish Home (3 verses and chorus.) Air - "My Old Kentucky Home." Words written by John L. Zieber, expressly for Mr. J. P. Gannon, the young Irish Comedian and Vocalist, and sung by him only. [Philadelphia]: Johnson, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. Wolf 1505c.
- 258. My Gum a Rubber Boots. - Go it rubber boots and save my pantalets (3 verses and chorus.) Air.: "Jordan Is a Hard Road to Travel." New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan military cupid, colored. See Wolf 1507.
- 259. My Highland Home. - My Highland home, where tempests blow (2 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan Ethiopian. Wolf 151 la.
- 260. My Johnny Was a Shoemaker. - My Johnny was a shoemaker (4 verses and chorus.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan clown. See Wolf 1514.
- 261. My Love He Is a Sailleur Boy 19 Y'rs Old. - My love, he is a sailleur boy, so gallant and bold (4 verses and chorus.) A sung with unbounded applause, by that Inimitable delineator of Ethiopian Characteristics, Dan Bryant. New York: H. De Marsan, ©1860. Border De Marsan fountain, colored. Not in Wolf.
- 262. My Love She Vas a Radish Girl Only 16 Years Old. - Mine love, she vas a radeesh gal, shust sixdeen years old (7 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Not in Wolf.
- 263. My Own Dear Home. - In foreign lands I longed to roam (4 verses and chorus.) Second song: "Orphan Boy's Song of Home". New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. Not in Wolf.
- 264. My Own Native Land. - I've roamed over mountains, I've crossed over floods (3 verses.) Second song: "Happy Land". New York: Andrews, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. See Wolf 1530.
- 265. My Poor Dog Tray. - On the green banks of Shannon, when Shelah was nigh (6 verses.) [New York]: Andrews, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. Wolf 1531.
- 266. My True Love Is a Butcher Boy. - My true love is a Butcher Boy, I would have you all to know (6 verses.) Air - "The Sailleur Boy". Composed by J. J. Allen. New York: H. De Marsan, ©1860. Border: Dc Marsan clown, colored. Wolf 1534.
- 267. Nancy Bell or Old Pine Tree. - Oh darkies, now I'm going to sing (3 verses and 2 choruses.) New York: Andrews, n.d. Border: Andrews ivy. Wolf 1536a.
- 268. Nancy Hill. - I've traveled over mountains (4 verses and chorus.) Air - "Home o'er the Mountains". By John Cross. New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan kissing cupids, colored. Not in Wolf.
- 269. National Song. Clime Beneath Whose genial Sun. - Clime, beneath whose genial sun (3 verses.) Air: "Scots Wha Hae Wi' Wallace Bled." New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan musical instruments, colored. Not in Wolf.
- 270. Nellie of the North. - The watch-fires are gleaming-the bright stars so beaming (2 verses and 2 choruses.) Air - "Annie of the Vale". By John Ross Dix. New York: Charles Magnus, n.d. Letter paper, blue ink. Headpiece: Magnus 234a, colored. Wolf 1567b.
- 271. Nelly Bray. - In a silent little corner of the old church-yard (3 verses and chorus.) Air -"Nettie Moore". By Thomas Sloan Jr., author of the popular song "Kitty Wells". New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. Not in Wolf.
- 272. Nettie Is No More. - In a little loney cottage by the shady mountain side (3 verses and chorus.) Air - "Nettie Moore". Composed by John Benjamin and sung by H. Greenwood, at the Chatham Theatre. New York: H. De Marsan, ©1860. Border: De Marsan trapper, colored. Wolf 1573a.
- 273. Nettie Moore. - In a little white cottage where the trees are ever green (5 verses and chorus.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan Ethiopian. Wolf 1574.
- 274. New England. - New England, I love thee, thou land of the free! (5 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan musical instruments, colored. Not in Wolf.
- 275. New Red, White, and Blue. - For Freedom, the soul of our nation (4 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan kissing cupids. Wolf 1983b.
- 276. The New Sebastopol. - Sebastopol will soon he taken/The French are now advancing, and to the walls are near (6 verses and 6 choruses.) Tune - "Hop de dooden do". Philadelphia: G. S. Harris, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. Not in Wolf.
- 277. De Nigger on de Fence. - Now, listen to me, white folks, de truth I'm going to tell you (6 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan Ethiopian. Wolf 1600b or c.
- 278. No One to Love. No one to love, none to caress (3 verses and chorus.) As sung by Abecco. Second song: "The Melodies of Many Lands." San Francisco: T. C. Boyd, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. See Wolf 1611.
- 279. Ode on Shanghai Mary Engine Co. 6. - I hope you'll pay attention (8 verses.) By a Runner. New York: J. Andrews, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. Wolf 1648.
- 280. Oh! and He Loved Me Dearly! - There was a nice young man came a courting of me (4 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, 0c1860. Border: De Marsan trapper. Wolf 1652a.
- 281. Oh! Boys, Carry Me 'Long. - Oh! carry me 'long (3 verses and chorus.) [New York?: Andrews?], n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. Wolf 1654a?
- 282. Oh, Breathe not Her Name. - Oh, breathe not her name! for it steals to my heart (2 verses.) Words by L. A Jones - Music by Frederick Buckley. Second song: "Choice of a Wife." New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. Wolf 1655.
- 283. Oh, Let Me Dream of Former Years! - Oh! let me dream of former years (3 verses and chorus.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. Wolf 1670a.
- 284. Oh, Let Me Go to My Home Again. - Oh, let me go to my home again (3 verses.) Second song: "Oh! for Wings to Soar." New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan musical instruments, colored. See Wolf 1671.
- 285. Oh! Silber Shining Moon. - Last night de moon was beaming (3 verses and chorus.) New York: J. Andrews, n.d. Border: Andrews ivy. Wolf 1680a.
- 286. Oh! Write Me a Song of My Father. - Oh! write me a song of my Father (3 verses and chorus.) Song and Chorus written and composed by C. Henry. New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan kissing cupids. Wolf 1686.
- 287. The Old Bog-Hole. - The pig is in the mire, and the cow is on the grass (4 verses and 2 choruses.) Air - "Old Zip Coon". New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan clown. See Wolf 1694.
- 288. The Old Brown Cot. - Among the scenes to memory dear (3 verses and chorus.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan Ethiopian, colored. Wolf 1695.
- 289. The Old Country Party. - Say, did ye iver go till an ould country party (8 verses.) Air - "Irishman's Shanty". By Harry M. Palmer. New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan horned imp. Wolf 1700a.
- 290. The Old Folks Are Gone. - Far, far in many lands I've wander'd (3 verses and chorus.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan comic heads, colored. Wolf 1706a.
- 291. The Old Folks Down on the Farm. - Oh, darkies, all draw near to me (3 verses and chorus.) New York: Andrews, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. Not in Wolf.
- 292. Old K. Y. KY. - De snow am in de cloud (6 verses and chorus.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan Ethiopian. Wolf 1715a.
- 293. Old Parson Brown. - Not long ago, in our town (6 verses and prose dialogue.) Air.: "The Rakes of Mallow." New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan comic heads, colored. Wolf 1725.
- 294. The Old Play Ground. - I'm sitting to-day in the old play ground (2 verses and 2 choruses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan kissing cupids, colored. Wolf 1727c.
- 295. Old Rosin the Beau. - I have travelled this wide world over (7 verses and chorus.) New York: J. Andrews, n.d. Border: Andrews ivy. Wolf 1728a.
- 296. One Foot in the Stirrup. - "One foot in the stirrup, one hand in the rein" (7 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan comic heads, colored. Wolf 1750.
- 297. One Good Turn Deserves Another. - The light of wisdom dimly burns (3 verses and chorus.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan Ethiopian. See Wolf 1751.
- 298. O'Toole & McFinnigan on the War. - Two Irishman out of employ (6 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan comic heads. See Wolf 1764.
- 299. Our Battle-Flag. - 0, never mind, boys! raise me up once again (3 verses and chorus.) Written by Edward Willett. Philadelphia: Johnson, n.d. Border: Auner-Johnson. Wolf 1768b.
- 300. Our Fifer-Boy. - While the battle was raging (8 verses.) Composed by C. G. Wright, on board the U.S. Steam-Ship Mississippi, (New-Orleans.) Air: "James Bird; or Dying Californian." New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan ship. Wolf 1778b.
- 301. Our Grand-Father's Days. - A song for to please all my kind friends before me (5 verses.) Written by John F. Poole. - Sung by Tony Pastor. New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan clown. Wolf 1791c.
- 302. Our Own Flag of Green. - Soon, soon shall our Green Flag wave 0'er us (4 verses and chorus.) Air - "Red, White, and Blue". New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan fountain. Wolf 1796a.
- 303. Paddy Murphy's Auction. - Now, Gintlemin, we'll soon begin: there's seats for those that walk in (7 verses?) Air: "Whack row de dow!" Sung by Tony Pastor. New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Not in Wolf.
- 304. Paddy O'Neil. - Ye sons of Hibernia, who snug on dry land (5 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan Ethiopian, colored. Not in Wolf.
- 305. Paddy's Land. - Oh, I've lately come to town, and for Ireland l am bound (4 verses and chorus.) Philadelphia: J. H. Johnson, n.d. Not in Wolf. 2 copies
- 306. Paddy Whack. - Oh, here lam and that is flat (5 verses and chorus.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan military cupid, colored. Wolf 1822.
- 307. Pat of Mullingar. - They may talk of Flying Children (6 verses and chorus.) As sung by Joe English. New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan ship with war scenes in lower corners. Not in Wolf.
- 308. Petticoat Lane. - When to Dublin I came from the sweet County Down (8 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan comic heads. Wolf 1871.
- 309. Phelim Mavourneen. - Oh, Phelim, dear Phelim! tho' lonely you wait (4 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan clown. See Wolf 1872.
- 310. Phoebe Dearest. - Phoebe, dearest, tell, oh! tell me (3 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan kissing cupids. Wolf 1876b.
- 311. The Pilot. - When lightnings pierce the pitchy sky (4 verses.) Second song: "Ever of Thee. New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan ship, colored. Wolf 1886.
- 312. Pirate of the Isles. - A hearty band I do command (4 verses and 2 choruses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan comic heads, colored. Not in Wolf.
- 313. Pity the Sorrows of a Poor Old Man. - Pity the sorrows of a poor old man! (10 verses.) By the Rev. Thomas Ross. New York: Andrews, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. Wolf 1889a.
- 314. Played Out. - New By-words come up every year (9 verses and chorus.) As sung by Tony Pastor. Air: "King and Countryman." New York: H. De Marsan, 0c1860. Border: De Marsan trapper. See Wolf 1891.
- 315. Pocahontas. - Upon the barren sand (3 verses and four line narrative.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan Ethiopian. Wolf 1894a.
- 316. Poor Billy Vail. - 'Twas a cold raw night (4 verses and chorus.) A Parody on "Lilly Dale." New York: J. Andrews, n.d. Border: Andrews ivy. Wolf 1898a.
- 317. The Poor Little Soldier's Boy. - The snow was fast a falling (4 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan military cupid. Wolf 1901b.
- 318. Poor Old Mike. - I was reared in Doncaster, some forty years ago (6 verses and chorus.) New York: H. De Marsan comic heads. See Wolf 1904.
- 319. The Poor Soldier Boy. - Gather a round me, one and all, short and tall, great and small (6 verses.) Words by Patrick Hayes. Air - "Bold Soldier Boy." New York: J. Andrews, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. See Wolf 1906.
- 320. Poor Tom the Greek. - It was on the twenty-second of June, from New York we set sail (9 verses.) Air - "Flowers of Edinburg." By Capt. Jack Ratling. N.p., n.d. Border: Double line with typographical ornament in comers. Not in Wolf.
- 321. Pop Goes the Question! - Matrimony is a nut (10 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan clown. See Wolf 1909.
- 322. The Post-Boy's Song. - The night is dark, and the way is long (4 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan Ethiopian, colored. Not in Wolf.
- 323. Pretty Sally. - 'Tis o'er the mountains far away (3 verses and chorus.) Philadelphia: Johnson, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. Wolf 1927a.
- 324. The Quill of the Concert Saloon. - I'll sing to you of a poor little quill, d[sic] I guess you've all seen him about (8 verses.) Air - "Sally of the Sewing Machine". New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan comic heads, colored. See Wolf 1947.
- 325. Red Petticoats. - Down Broadway, ere the sun was low (7 verses.) By Willie E. Pabor. New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan ship, colored. Wolf 1979.
- 326. Rockaway. - On old Long Island's sea girt shore (3 verses and chorus.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan Ethiopian. Wolf 2021.
- 327. The Rock Beside the Sea. - Oh, tell me not the woods are fair (2 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan Ethiopian. See Wolf 2018.
- 328. The Rock Beside the Sea. - Oh, tell me not the woods are fair (2 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan clown, colored. See Wolf 2018.
- 329. Rock Beside the Sea. - Oh, tell me not the woods are fair (2 verses.) Second song: "Laurie's Cottage." Philadelphia: J. H. Johnson, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. See Wolf 2018.
- 330. Rock Me to Sleep, Mother. - Backward, turn backward, 0 time, in your flight! (3 verses and chorus.) Words by Florence Percy. Music by Ernest Leslie. New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan military cupid. See Wolf 2019.
- 331. The Rocky Road to Dublin. - In the merry month of June (7 verses and chorus.) Sung by William Carleton. Air - Irish jig. New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan ship with war scenes in lower corners. Not in Wolf.
- 332. Roll on Silver Moon. - As I strayed from my cot at the close of day (3 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, ©1860. Border: De Marsan fountain, colored. See Wolf 2023.
- 333. Root Hog or Die. - I'll tell you of a story that happened long ago (7 verses.) Sung with shouts of Applause all over the country in Madigan & Co's National Travelling Circus. New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan comic heads, colored. Wolf 2025a.
- 334. Root Hog or Die! No 2. - The greatest old Nigger that I ever did see (4 verses and chorus.) Composed and Sung with Unbounded Applause by Richard J. McGowan, the World Renowned Champion Banjoist. New York: Andrews, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. Wolf 2026a.
- 335. Root Hog or Die! No.3. - I am a jolly nigger as ever you did see (5 verses and chorus.) Composed and Sung by C. Morrell, Banjoist. New York: Andrews, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament, colored. See Wolf 2027.
- 336. Root Hog or Die! No.3. - I am a jolly nigger as ever you did see (5 verses and chorus.) Composed and Sung by C. Morrell, Banjoist. New York: Andrews, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. See Wolf 2027.
- 337. Root Hog or Die. No.4. - I am de greatest little darkey on de top ob de earth (4 verses and chorus.) Composed and sung by Wm. H. Core, the Young Banjoist. New York: Andrews, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament, colored. See Wolf 2028a.
- 338. Root Hog or Die. No. 4. - I am de greatest little darkey on de top ob de earth (4 verses and chorus.) Composed and sung by Wm. H. Core, the Young Banjoist. New York: Andrews, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. See Wolf 2028a.
- 339. Root Hog or Die. No. 5. - Come, listen to my story, and a good one I'll relate (6 verses). Written on board U.S. Gunboat Com. Barneyey, after the Battle at Newbern, N.C. - By a Blue-Jacket. New York: D. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan horned imp. Wolf 2029a.
- 340. Rory O'More. - Young Rory O'More courted Kathleen Bawn (3 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan military cupid. See Wolf 2030.
- 340a. Rory O'More. - Young Rory O'More courted Kathleen Bawn (3 verses.) New York: Andrews, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. Wolf 2030a.
- 341. Rosalie the Prairie Flower. - On the distant prairie, where the heather wild (3 verses and chorus.) New York: H. De Marsan, ©1860. Border: De Marsan fountain, colored. Wolf 2032a.
- 342. Rosa's Wedding Day. -0, name de spot, and tell me where (4 verses and chorus.) Philadelphia: Johnson, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. Not in Wolf.
- 343. The Rose and the Lily. - In the gay month of June, a fair blushing rose (5 verses and chorus.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan fountain. Wolf 2033 a.
- 344. Rose Atherton. - The summer days are coming (3 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan Ethiopian, colored. Wolf 2034.
- 345. The Rose of Alabama. - Away from Mississippi's vale (7 verses and chorus.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan Ethiopian, colored. Wolf 2035.
- 346. Rose of Tennessee. - 'Twas on a summer morning all in de month of June (3 verses and chorus.) Composed by Dan Eletcher. Philadelphia: Harris, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. Not in Wolf.
- 347. Roy's Wife of Aldivalloch. - Roy's wife ofAldi valloch (4 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, ©1860. Border: De Marsan trapper, colored. Wolf 2044.
- 348. Sad News from Home. - Sad news from home for me (3 verses and chorus.) [New York?: Andrews?], n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. Wolf 2049?
- 349. Saint Patrick's Day. No.2. - You, Sons of the Gael, wherever you kneel (12 verses.) No. 1058. Boston: Horace Partridge, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. Not in Wolf.
- 350. Sairy Sykes. - To me said mother, t'other day (3? verses of uneven length.) As sung by Master George. [Philadelphia]: Johnson, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. See Wolf 2055.
- 351. Sairy Sykes. - To me said mother t'other day (6 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan comic heads, colored. See Wolf 2055.
- 352. Sambo, I Have Missed You. - Oh, Sambo, it is you, dear, come down to see me now (3 verses.) By John Allen. New York: Andrews, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. Wolf 2061.
- 353. Sandy and Jenny. - "Come, come, bonny lassie," cried Sandy, "a wa (6 verses.) New York:. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan Ethiopian, colored. Wolf 2064.
- 354. Savoureen Deelish Eileen Oge. - Ah! the moment was sad, when my Love and I parted (4 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan military cupid. Wolf 2070.
- 355. Scenes That Are Brightest. - Scenes that are brightest may charm awhile (2 verses.) From Maritana. Second song: "Nature's Woodland Call." New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan horned imp. Not in Wolf.
- 356. She Danced Like a Fairy. - I'll relate to you, Public, the source of my woes (5 verses and chorus.) Sung by the celebrated Charles Vivian. New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan military cupid. Not in Wolf.
- 357. Sheepskin, Beeswax. - Now I'm gwine to sing a song (5 verses and chorus.) As sung nightly with thunders of Applause, by Dan Emmit, at White's Melodeon, 53 Bowery, N.Y. New York: J. Andrews, n.d. Border: Andrews ivy. Wolf 2093a.
- 358. Shelling Green Peas. - I sing you a ditty of a damsel so pretty (5 verses and chorus.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan Ethiopian. Not in Wolf.
- 359. She Never Blam'd Him, Never. - She never blam'd him, never (4 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan musical instruments, colored. Wolf 2088.
- 360. She's Handsome as a Rose. Or She Was Such a Charmer. - I'll sing to you a song (3 verses and chorus.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan clown. Not in Wolf.
- 361. She Was Such a Nice Young Gal. - Blow on, ye winds, and crack your cheeks (6 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan harp, colored. See Wolf 2090.
- 362. She Wore a Wreath of Roses. - She wore a wreath of roses (3 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan Ethiopian, colored. Wolf 2091a
- 363. Sing Me to Sleep My Mother. - Sing me to sleep, my mother (4 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. See Wolf 2117.
- 364. Sleeping I Dream, Love. - Sleeping I dream 'd, love, dream 'd, love, of thee (2 verses.) Second song: "Oh, Whisper What Thou Feelest!" New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan horned imp. See Wolf 2129.
- 365. Sleigh Bell Song. - Jingle, jingle, jingle, jingle, clear the way (4 verses and chorus.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan comic heads, colored. Not in Wolf.
- 366. Smiggy McGuirrel. - I had a son, he came from the war (3 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan Ethiopian. Wolf 2130a.
- 367. Soda-Water Man. - Now all American citizens just listen to me (3 verses and chorus.) As sung by Dick McGowan the Celebrated Banjoist. New York: H. De Marsan, ©1860. Border: De Marsan clown, colored. Not in Wolf.
- 368. The Soldier's Child. - A mother sat by her open door (4 verses.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan military cupid. See Wolf 2142.
- 369. The Soldier's Dream. - Our bugles sang truce-for the night-cloud had lour'd (6 verses.) Second song: "The Soldier's Tear." New York: J. Andrews, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. See Wolf 2145.
- 370. The Soldier's Welcome Home. - From the camp and filed returning (3 verses and chorus.) New York: H. De Marsan, n.d. Border: De Marsan kissing cupids. See Wolf 2162.
- 371. Some One to Love. - Some one to love in this wide world of sorrow (2 verses and choruses.) New York: De Marsan, ©1860. Border: De Marsan fountain, colored. See Wolf 2165.
- 372. The Song of All Songs. No.2. - You've heard of many songs, but of one thing I'm sure(5 verses.) Air - "The Captain with His Whiskers." No.877. Boston: Horace Partridge, n.d. Border: Typographical ornament. See Wolf 2182.